bushdvd.com 2016-11-19

# Movie Rental XXX - Rent XXX DVDs Online - Adult Videos for Rent

Effective Date: 12/12/2014 

This privacy policy applies to http://www.bushdvd.com owned and operated by NoCash, Inc.. This privacy policy describes how NoCash, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: http://www.bushdvd.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

NoCash, Inc. has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://www.bushdvd.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact Jason Holt at [customerservice@bushdvd.com](mailto:customerservice@bushdvd.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request). 

Personal Information  
We do NOT collect any personal information about you except your name, mailing and shipping address, credit card information, and e-mail address. We collect this information to register our users for an account and through our "Contact Us" form so we can reply to inquiries from our customers. 

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. NoCash Inc. does NOT share, sell, or disseminate any of your personal information with any third parties. 

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. When shipping you an item your address is disclosed to the USPS. Note: The USPS does not know what is being shipped. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us. 

You do have the right to change any of the requested personal information. To change any of your personal information go to your account which can be found under the "Account" tab once you have logged in. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [customerservice@bushdvd.com](mailto:customerservice@bushdvd.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

If you choose to write a review on this Web site, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in the "Write a Review" portion of the web site. _To request removal of your personal information from the "Write a Review" page, contact us at[customerservice@bushdvd.com](mailto:customerservice@bushdvd.com)_. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

E-Mails  
We periodically send out promotional e-mails. We do send confirmational e-mails, such as shipment confirmations. If you wish to unsubscribe from receiving promotional emails from us, you may do so by sending an email to us with 'Unsubscribe' in the subject line or by changing your e-mail preferences on the account page. Please send this email to [customerservice@bushdvd.com](mailto:customerservice@bushdvd.com). 

Tracking Technologies  
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by NoCash, affiliates, or analytics. We use Google Analytics. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for _our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g. display preferences), and for authentication_. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

Analytics / Log Files  
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information. 

Security  
When you submit sensitive information such as credit card, and login information, your information is transmitted through a state of the art 128-bit SSL encryption. Also, encrypted are pages for our Affiliate Program where other sensitive information is collected, specifically social security number and Tax ID number. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [customerservice@bushdvd.com](mailto:customerservice@bushdvd.com). 

Social Media Features and Widgets  
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

Links to 3rd Party Sites 

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of NoCash, Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

Changes in this Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective. 

Business Transitions  
In the event NoCash, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified either via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

Contact Information  

> Address:  
>  NoCash, Inc.  
>  3148 Midway Dr  
>  San Diego, CA 92110  
> 
> 
> Phone:  
>  Call Us Toll Free! - 1-877-BUSHDVD (287-4383)   
> 
> 
> E-mail: [customerservice@bushdvd.com](mailto:customerservice@bushdvd.com)   
>
